Guide to the Papers of Mark Popovskii,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XV: Audio
  - Ivanov, […] (Box 46, Folder 46-54)
    [Vlasovets. Same tape as Novosil'tsov, Igor'.]
  - Kashtel'ian, Mikhail (Box 46, Folder 46-41)
    [same tape as Moisik, Liuba]
  - Krein, Anna (Box 46, Folder 46-1, 46-2, 46-3, 46-4)
  - Kriukov, […] (Box 46, Folder 46-5)
    [same tape as Arzunian, Valia]
  - Krichevskaia, Iulia (Box 46, Folder 46-6)
    [same tape as Ginsburg, Konstantin]
  - Kurant, Misha (Box 46, Folder 46-7)
  - Kurant, Raia (Box 46, Folder 46-7)
  - Kvitash, Vadim (Box 46, Folder 46-8, 46-9, 48-2)
    [same tapes as Feigin, Grigorii, Sokolov, Viktor (48-2)]
  - Liberovskaia, Katia (Box 46, Folder 46-10)
  - Liberovskii, Roman (Box 46, Folder 46-10, 46-11, 46-11A.)
  - Lifshits, Anna (Box 46, Folder 46-12)
    [same tape as Arzunian, Valia and Ed., Grinshtup, Grigorii and Elena.]
  - Lippe, Lorein (Box 46, Folder 46-13)
    [same tape as Natasha K.]
  - Lopukhina, Olia (Box 46, Folder 46-14)
  - Loskutova, Tania (Box 46, Folder 46-15, 46-16)
    [same tapes as: Alekseeva, Evelina (46-15), Fridman, Margarita and Zarydnye [family] (46-16)]
  - Lozovskii, Iurii (Box 46, Folder 46-17)
  - Magarshak, Iurii (Box 46, Folder 46-18)
  - Magarshak, Faina (Box 46, Folder 46-19, 46-20)
  - Magarshak, Grisha (Box 46, Folder 46-19)
  - Maiskaia, Tamara (Box 46, Folder 46-21, 46-22)
  - Makarenko, Liudmila (Box 46, Folder 46-23)
  - Makhuner, Albert (Box 46, Folder 46-24)
  - Maksimova, Liudmila (Box 46, Folder 46-25)
  - Maksimov, Sergei (Box 46, Folder 46-25, 46-26)
    [same tape as Golubintsev, Anatolii]
  - Mamiofa, Iosif (Box 46, Folder 26A)
  - Mamontov, Iurii (Box 46, Folder 46-27)
    [same tape as translation of article from Kanadian newspaper about the murder of Aleksandr Men' (translated by R. I. Kolesnikova) - possibly erased.]
  - Margulis, Mikhail (Box 46, Folder 46-28)
  - Markov, Albert (Box 46, Folder 46-29, 46-30)
  - Markov, Aleksandr (Box 46, Folder 46-29, 46-31)
  - Markova, Marina (Box 46, Folder 46-31)
  - Meendorf, Margarita (Box 46, Folder 46-32, 46-33)
  - Meier, IUrii (Box 46, Folder 46-34, 46-35)
  - Messner, Iurii (Box 46, Folder 46-36)
  - Men', Aleksandr (about) (Box 46, Folder 46-37, 46-27, 45-55)
    [radio broadcasts from Moscow in the day of Men's murder and on 40th day. Gift of Kolesnikova]
  - Milanovskii, Svet (Box 46, Folder 46-38)
  - Mil'shtein, Sam (Box 46, Folder 46-39)
  - Moishezon, B. (Box 46, Folder 46-40)
  - Moisik, Liuba (Box 46, Folder 46-41)
    [same tapes as Kashtel'ian, Mikhail (46-41), Moliver, Vladimir (46-45)]
  - Moldavan, Vadim (Box 46, Folder 46-42, 46-43, 46-44, 44-28)
    [same tapes as Potievskii, Aleks. (46-44) Chalova, Liudmila (44-28)]
  - Moliver, Vladimir (Box 46, Folder 46-41, 46-45)
    [same tapes as Dashevskii, Aleksandr (44-41), Moisik, Liuba (46-45)]
  - Moravskii, Nikita (Box 46, Folder 46-46)
  - Moravskii, Nikolai (Box 46, Folder 46-46)
  - Mordukhaeva, Irina (Box 46, Folder 46-47)
  - Murisenko, Liuba (Box 46, Folder 46-48)
  - Nizhnikov, Aleksandr (Box 46, Folder 46-49, 46-50)
  - Nizhnikova, Margarita (Box 46, Folder 46-49, 46-50)
  - Novosil'tsov, Igor' (Box 46, Folder 46-51, 46-52, 46-53, 46-54, 46-55)
    [same tapes as Ivanov, […] (46-54), Galina, Evgeniia (46-55)]
  - Ordyntsev, Aleksandr (Box 46, Folder 46-56)
    [same tape as Doroshevich, Vladimir]
  - Osherov, Vladimir (Box 46, Folder 46-57)
    [same tape as Vasilevs[kii], Misha]
  - Vasilevskii, Misha (Box 46, Folder 46-57)
    [same tape as Osherov, Vladimir]
  - Osman, David (Box 46, Folder 46-58, 46-59)
  - Brinker, Veronika (Box 47, Folder 47-27)
    [same tape as Radomskii, Arkadii]
  - Durnovo, Sonia (Box 47, Folder 47-57)
    [same tape as Sidorenko, Zhanna]
  - Fainshtein, Mikhail (Box 47, Folder 47-31)
    [same tape as Raevskii, Viktor]
  - Kheifets, Leonid (Box 47, Folder 47-44)
    [same tape as Shakhov, Vasilii]
  - Pak, Imre (Box 47, Folder 47-1)
  - Paleev, Mikhail (Box 47, Folder 47-2)
  - Pankrat, Ivan (Box 47, Folder 47-3)
  - Pankrat, Tania (Box 47, Folder 47-3)
  - Pankrat, Masha (Box 47, Folder 47-3)
  - Pantiukhov, Oleg (Box 47, Folder 47-4)
  - Parkhomenko, Vl. (Box 47, Folder 47-5)
  - Pavlovskaia, Evgeniia (Zhenia) (Box 47, Folder 47-6)
  - Petrov, Mikhail (Box 47, Folder 47-7)
  - Piatnochko, Ruf' (Box 47, Folder 47-8)
  - Pil'tser, IUrii (Box 47, Folder 47-9)
  - Pinskii, Mark (Box 47, Folder 47-10, 47-11)
  - Podgorbunskaia, Ania (Box 47, Folder 47-12)
  - Poliak, Alevtina (Box 47, Folder 47-13, 47-14)
    [same tape as going with Larisa Frumkina to the conference on bilingual education in American Schools(47-13)]
  - Po[pova], Faina (Box 47, Folder 47-15)
  - Poretskii, Leonid (Box 47, Folder 47-16)
  - Portnaia, Raia (Box 47, Folder 47-17)
  - Portnoi, Semen (Box 47, Folder 47-18)
  - Pozdeeva, Irina (Box 47, Folder 47-19, 48-28)
    [same tape as Trubetskoi, Sergei Grigorievich (48-28)]
  - Prais, Valerii (Box 47, Folder 47-20)
    [same tape as Krochek, Gennadii]
  - Prikhno, Igor (Box 47, Folder 47-21, 47-22, 47-23)
    [same tapes as Glupak, Sergei (47-23), […], Andrei, Lilia (47-22)]
  - […], Andrei, Lilia (Box 47, Folder 47-22)
  - Purto, Vitalii (Box 47, Folder 47-24)
  - Purto, Vika (Box 47, Folder 47-24)
  - Pushchin, Ivan (Box 47, Folder 47-25)
  - Rabinovich, Efim (Box 47, Folder 47-25A)
  - Radomskii, Arkadii (Box 47, Folder 47-26, 47-27)
    [same tape as Brinker, Veronika]
  - Radysh, Oksana (Box 47, Folder 47-28)
    [about Dabbert-Drozdovskaia, Aleksandra]
  - Raevskii, Robert (Box 47, Folder 47-29)
  - Raevskii, Viktor (Box 47, Folder 47-30, 47-31)
    [same tape as Fainshtein, Mikhail]
  - Raikin, Viktor (Box 47, Folder 47-32)
  - Rannit, Tatiana (Box 47, Folder 47-33)
    [same tape as Vasilov family]
  - Vasilov family (Box 47, Folder 47-33)
    [same tape as Rannit, Tatiana]
  - Rappoport, Vitalii (Box 47, Folder 47-33A)
  - Rappoport, Katia (Box 47, Folder 47-33A)
  - Rappoport, Kolia (Box 47, Folder 47-33A)
  - Rogovaia, Lilia (Box 47, Folder 47-34)
  - Rubinshtein, Lev (Box 47, Folder 47-35, 47-36)
  - Ruslanov, Anatolii (Box 47, Folder 47-37, 47-38, 47-39)
  - Sergeev, Viktor (Box 47, Folder 47-40)
  - Sergeeva, Natasha (Box 47, Folder 47-40)
  - Shadrin, Valerii (Box 47, Folder 47-41, 47-42)
  - Shadrina, Natasha (Box 47, Folder 47-41, 47-42)
  - Shaginian, Natasha (Box 47, Folder 47-43)
  - Shakhov, Vasilii (Box 47, Folder 47-44)
    [same tape as Kheifets, Leonid]
  - Shapiro, Genrikh (Box 47, Folder 47-45)
  - Shcherbatov, Aleksei (Box 47, Folder 47-46)
  - Shenker, Ilia (Box 47, Folder 47-47)
  - Shevelev, Vladimir (Box 47, Folder 47-48)
  - Sheveleva, Anna (Box 47, Folder 47-49)
    [same tape as Daianaev, Lev]
  - Shnaider, Mikhail (Box 47, Folder 47-50, 47-51)
  - Shtein, Eduard (Box 47, Folder 47-52, 47-53)
  - Shtil'man, Artur (Box 47, Folder 47-54)
    [same tape as Kalina, Aleksandr biography]
  - Kalina, Aleksandr (Box 47, Folder 47-54)
    [same tape as Shtil'man, Artur]
  - Shtivel', Ruslan (Box 47, Folder 47-55)
  - Shuksta, Aleksandr (Box 47, Folder 47-56)
  - Sidorenko, Zhanna (Box 47, Folder 47-57)
    [same tape as Durnovo, Sonia]
  - Simuk, Konstantin (Box 47, Folder 47-58)
  - Simuk, Elena (Box 47, Folder 47-58)
  - Skidan, Lidia (Box 47, Folder 47-59)
  - Skidan, Aleksei (Box 47, Folder 47-59)
  - Skaruffi, Ellen (Box 47, Folder 47-60)
    [Curator, Bakhmeteff Archive]
  - Kamenkovich, Irina (Box 48, Folder 48-27)
    [same tape as Troll', IUlia]
  - Kalinin, Vasilii (Box 48, Folder 48-22)
    [same tape as Tolstaia, Masha]
  - Lipkovich, Iakov (Box 48, Folder 48-5)
    [Literaturnyi Cleveland. same tape as Sorokoumova, Sasha]
  - Pokrass, Tatiana (Box 48, Folder 48-17)
    [same tape as Tikhonov, Iakov]
  - Smelianskaia, Svetlana (Box 48, Folder 48-1)
  - Sokolov, Viktor (Box 48, Folder 48-2)
    [same tape as Kvitash, Vadim]
  - Zarudnaia, Elena (Box 48, Folder 48-46, 46-16)
    [same tapes as Loskutova, Tania (46-16), Friman, Margarita (48-46)]
  - Sokol'skii, Arkadii (Box 48, Folder 48-3)
  - Sorokoumova, Sasha (Box 48, Folder 48-4, 48-5)
    [same tape as Lipkovich, Iakov (Literaturnyi Cleveland)]
  - Stainer, Zoia (Box 48, Folder 48-6)
  - Stesin, Sasha (Box 48, Folder 48-7)
  - Strazhnik, Svetlana (Box 48, Folder 48-8)
  - Sudakov, Oskar (Box 48, Folder 48-9)
  - Sudakov, Stepan (Box 48, Folder 48-10)
  - Suslov, Mikhail (Box 48, Folder 48-20)
    [same tape as Tolstaia, Ol'ga]
  - Sverdlin, Anatolii (Box 48, Folder 48-11, 48-12)
    [tape 48-12 includes Zal'tsberg, Mark about Sverdlin]
  - Tabachnik, Ben (Box 48, Folder 48-13)
  - Tameev, Boris (Box 48, Folder 48-14)
  - Tikhonov, IAkov (Box 48, Folder 48-15, 48-16, 48-17)
    [same tape as Pokrass, Tatiana]
  - Titel'man, [Grigorii] (Box 48, Folder 48-18)
  - Tolmaz[in], D. (Box 48, Folder 48-19)
  - Tolstaia, Ol'ga (Box 48, Folder 48-20, 48-21)
    [same tapes as Suslov, Mikhail (48-20), Rodzianko, Tatiana (48-21)]
  - Rodzianko, Tatiana (Box 48, Folder 48-21)
    [Maiden name: Lopukhina. Same tape as Tolstaia, Olga.]
  - Tolstaia, Masha (Box 48, Folder 48-22)
    [same tape as Kalinin, Vasilii]
  - Troitskii, Nikolai (Box 48, Folder 48-23, 48-24, 48-25, 48-26)
  - Troll', IUlia (Box 48, Folder 48-27)
    [reading about Dr. Gaaz. same tape as Kamenkovich, Irina]
  - Trubetskoi, Sergei Grigorievich (Box 48, Folder 48-28)
    [same tape as Pozdeeva, Irina]
  - Trubetskoi, Sergei Alekseevich (Box 48, Folder 48-29)
    [Tolstovskii fond]
  - Tsukurova, Olga (Box 48, Folder 48-30)
  - Tsuriupa, Aleksei (Box 48, Folder 48-31)
  - Vasil'ev, Anatolii (Box 48, Folder 48-32)
  - Vasil'ev, Igor' (Box 48, Folder 48-33)
  - Vasilevskii, Misha (Box 48, Folder 48-33A)
  - Velikosel'skaia, Liudmila (Box 48, Folder 48-34)
  - Voevodskaia, Kseniia (Box 48, Folder 48-41)
    [same tape as Zaitseva, Svetlana]
  - Volokh, Anna (Box 48, Folder 48-35)
    [editor, MovieLine]
  - Vol'pert, Ada (Box 48, Folder 48-36)
  - Von Hagen, Mark (Box 48, Folder 48-37)
  - Zabezhanskaia, Marina (Box 48, Folder 48-38)
  - Zaitseva, Svetlana (Box 48, Folder 48-39, 48-40, 48-41)
    [same tape as Voevodskaia, Kseniia]
  - Zal'tsberg, Mark (Box 48, Folder 48-42, 48-43, 48-44, 48-12)
    [about Sverdlin, Anatolii (48-11, 48-42)]
  - Zal'tsman, Iosif (Box 48, Folder 48-45)
  - Zaslavskii, Vitalii (Box 48, Folder 48-47, 48-48)
    [same tape as Leibovich, Arnold]
  - Leibovich, Arnold (Radik) (Box 48, Folder 48-48)
  - Zelenyi, Petr (Box 48, Folder 48-49, 48-50)
  - Zelenskaia, Nella (Box 48, Folder 48-51)
  - Zheleznyi, Egor (Box 48, Folder 48-52, 48-53)
  - Zhivotin, Aleksandr (Box 48, Folder 48-54)
    [same tape as Chubareva, Natasha]
  - Chubareva, Natasha (Box 48, Folder 48-54)
    [same tape as Zhivotin, Aleksandr]
  - Whiteside, Duncan (Box 48, Folder 48-55, 48-56)
    [president, Maidstone Foundation]
  - Last names not known (Box 48, Folder 48-57 - 48-70)
  - Odessa - 200th Anniversary (Box 48, Folder 48-71)
  - Baltimore, Dec. 1997 (Box 48, Folder 48-72)
  - Chicago - Festival' Russkogo Iskusstva, Nov. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 48-73)
    [Festival of Russian Art]